Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1925-1984; Series I; 15.5; (31 boxes)
  - Villon, François
    - "Villon's Epitaph" and "Ballade: A Modern Version," galley., undated (Box 28, Folder 1968)
      With: note to William [Cookson] from Peter [Dale], undated
  - Vinokurov, Evgenii Mikhailovich (Vinokurov, Yevgeni)
    - Untitled poem, translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1969)
  - Virgil
    - "Eclogue 4," translated by Tim Ades, galley, with translator's corrections, undated (Box 28, Folder 1970)
    - "Three Inscriptions for Statues of Priapus," (attributed to Virgil), translated by John Heath-Stubbs
      - Typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1971)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 28, Folder 1972)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1973)
  - Vollmar, Jim
    - "The Placing of the Rook," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1974)
  - Wade, Stephen
    - [Review] " Cross Channel by Peter Dale"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1975)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 Jul 26 (Box 28, Folder 1976)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1977)
    - [Review] "Ewart Milne"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1978)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1979)
    - "An Essay on the Dramas of Tennyson," typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1980)
    - "Old Man," typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1981)
    - "Peter Dale's 'Cell': Allegory and Personal Authority," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1982)
    - [Review] "Peter Dent: Distant Lamps ," typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1983)
    - "Stevie Smith and the Untruth of Myth"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1984)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 Jun 22 (Box 28, Folder 1985)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from Stephen Wade, 1977 Jun 22
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1986)
    - "Their Love," typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 1987)
    - [Review] " Too Much of Water "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 28, Folder 1988)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 28, Folder 1989)
  - Wainwright, Jeffrey
    - "Children in Winter"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 1990)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 1991)
    - [Review] "An Essay on Geoffrey Hill's Tenebrae "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1992)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 1993)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1994)
    - "Geoffrey Hill's 'Lachrimae'"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1995)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 1996)
    - [Review] "Peter Levi's Collected Poems "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1997)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1998)
    - [Review] "Poetry and Revolution: Alexander Blok and Osip Mandelstam"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 1999)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 2000)
    - "William Wordsworth at Briggflatts"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2001)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 2002)
  - Walkiewicz, E. P.
    - "A Reading of Canto CXX," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2003)
  - Wang Hsin-Fu (Wang, David Rafael)
    - "Chinese Folk Poems," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2004)
  - Wang, Hsiao-hi (Wang Xiaoni)
    - "A Pair of Shoes at the Edge of the Field," printed version, undated (Box 29, Folder 2004a)
  - Wang, Hsin-ti (Wang Xindi)
    - "Spring is Coming," printed version, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 2004b)
  - Wang, Jung (Wang Rong)
    - "The Heights of Mount Wu," and "Miscellaneous Poem," translated by John Cayley, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2005)
    - "The Heights of Mount Wu," translated by Dick Davis, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2006)
    - "The Heights of Mount Wu," translated by Caroline Wright, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2007)
    - "The Heights of Witch Mountain," translated by Roland John, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2008)
    - "The Heights of Witch Mountain," translated by Desmond O'Grady, typescript, 1982 Nov (Box 29, Folder 2009)
  - Wang, Jung (Wang Rong) and Wu Chun (Wu Jun)
    - "The Heights of Wu Mountain" and "In the Mountains," unidentified translator, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2010)
    - Empty folder (Box 29, Folder 2011)
  - Ward, J. P.
    - "But Lowell He Did Not Touch a seeing of self and history," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2012)
  - Warner, Val
    - "'Loyal to Water': A Reading of the Poetry of Michael Hamburger"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2013)
      - Typescript, corrected, p.9-12, 16, 29, undated (Box 29, Folder 2014)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 2015)
    - [Review] " Out for the Elements ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2016)
  - Whigham, Peter
    - Astapovo
      - "Contents" and " Tradition 1," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2017)
      - "Identity 2," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2018)
      - "[Discrimination] 3," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2019)
      - "Home," poem number 4 of Astapovo, musical score, undated (Box 29, Folder 2020)
      - "Robin Hood/Maid Marion 5," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2021)
      - "Violence Swaddles All (Love-) Acts Before & After," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2022)
      - "Anti-Vietnam War Poem," poem number 12 of Astapovo, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2023)
      - "In the Pass," poem 13 of Astapovo, typescript, 2c., undated (Box 29, Folder 2024)
      - "Journey" poem 14 of Astapovo, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2025)
      - "Memory," poem 16 of Astapovo, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2026)
      - "Villon on Death," poem 17 of Astapovo, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2027)
      - "[A - Z] 18," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2028)
      - "1," "6," and "18," from Astapovo, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2029)
      - "From 'Astapovo' or What Are We to Do?," printed version
        See: Oversize, Box 57, folder 2794
    - "The Cheated Heart," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2030)
    - "Eternity," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2031)
    - "V," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2032)
    - "Golden Age," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2033)
    - "Herakleitos - an Indian dialogue," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2034)
    - "His Wife," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2035)
    - "Il Suo Paradiso Terrestre," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2036)
    - "The Ingathering of Love," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2037)
    - "Justice Is Invisible...," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2038)
    - "Love Poems of the VIth Dalai Lama," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2039)
    - "The Love Songs of the VIth Dalai Lama (1683-1706)," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2040)
    - "May Banners," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2041)
    - "My Bohemian (Fantasy)," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2042)
    - "My Heart, Those Sheets of Blood...," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2043)
    - "The New Bride," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2044)
    - [Nine Poems], typescript, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 2045)
    - "Nostalgia for C. L. M.," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2046)
    - "On the Pier," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2047)
    - "VI. The poet secretly imprints his own image in his mistress' looking glass," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2048)
    - [Seven Poems], typescript, 1970, undated (Box 29, Folder 2049)
    - "Song of the Highest Tower," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2050)
    - "To Patrick Swift," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2051)
    - "Trumpets," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2052)
    - Untitled poem from The Fletcher Songbook?, typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2053)
  - Whigham, Peter, (translator)
    - "Six Epigrams from Martial," typescript, 1981 Aug 14 (Box 29, Folder 2054)
    - "Versions of Virgil, Catullus and Martial," [Martial is missing], typescript, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 2055)
  - Widdess, Helen
    See: Caroline Wright, Box 30 folder 2077
  - Whitby, Julie
    - "After 'The Road in Louveciennes' by Camille Pissarro," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2056)
    - "Exile," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2057)
    - "Off Stage"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2058)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1984 Jul 18 (Box 29, Folder 2059)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from Julie Whitby, 1984 Jul 18
  - Wilcockson, Colin
    - "David Jones and 'The Break,"' typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2060)
    - "The King Speaks to His Bishop," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2061)
    - "Letters of David Jones in the Possession of Merton College," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2062)
    - "Notes on Some Letters of David Jones"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2063)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 2064)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2065)
    - "Reunions," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2066)
  - William, Duke of Aquitaine
    - "Two Poems," trans. by Roger Sharrock
      - Typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2067)
      - Galley, with translator's corrections, undated (Box 29, Folder 2068)
  - Williams, Evan Gwyn
    - "The Dancer and the Tale," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2069)
  - Williamson, Alan
    - "Friends Who Have Failed"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2070)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2071)
    - "The Reshaping of 'Waking Early Sunday Morning," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2072)
  - Wilmer, Clive
    - [Review] " The New Oxford Book of Christian Verse chosen and edited by Donald Davie," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2073)
  - Witemeyer, High
    - [Review] "Ronald Bush: The Genesis of Ezra Pound's Cantos ," typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2074)
    - [Reviews] "Some Recent Studies of Ezra Pound"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 2075)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 29, Folder 2076)
  - Wright, Caroline
    - "Five Poems," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2077)
    - "Girl on the Quay, Night"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2078)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2079)
    - "Leaves"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2080)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2081)
    - "Wind Pictures," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2082)
    - Untitled poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2083)
  - Wright, Caroline and Helen Widdess
    - "Thinking of Having a Baby," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2084)
  - Wright, David
    - "Approaches to the City"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2085)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2086)
    - "Borrowdale Yews," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2087)
    - "Canons Ashby II"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2088)
      - Galley, undated (Box 30, Folder 2089)
    - "E. P. at Westminster," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2090)
    - "The Hotel," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2091)
    - [Review] "John Heath-Stubbs"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2092)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2093)
    - "Notes on a Jubilee," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2094)
    - "Notes on Hardy"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2095)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2096)
    - "A Personal Prosody"
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2097)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2098)
    - [Review] "The Poetry of C. H. Sisson"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2099)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2100)
    - "Remembering Tennyson," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2101)
    - "Stevie Smith and Thomas Blackburn"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2102)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2103)
    - "Three Poems from A South African Album ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2104)
    - "Triptych," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 30, Folder 2105)
    - "Two Memorial Sonnets," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2106)
  - Wright, Jean
    - [Review] "Bread for the Winter Birds"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2107)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 30, Folder 2108)
  - Wu, Chun (Wu Jun)
    - "In the Mountains," translated by John Cayley, typescript, 1982 Nov 5 (Box 30, Folder 2109)
    - "In the Mountains," translated by Dick Davis, typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2110)
    - "In the Mountains," translated by Roland John, typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2111)
    - "In the Mountains," translated by Desmond O' Grady, typescript, 1982 Nov (Box 30, Folder 2112)
    - "In the Mountains," translated by Caroline Wright, typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2113)
      See also: Jung Wang (Wang Rong)
  - Wylie, Andrew
    - "Sculpture in Metal of Richard Brotman," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2114)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2115)
  - Yang, Wan-Li
    - "Returning Home the Next Day After Drinking," translated by John Cayley, typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2116)
  - Yeh, Yen-pin (Ye Yanbin)
    - "Lamp, a Burning Heart," "Two Towels Hung on the Wire" and "Night, the Quiet Night," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 30, Folder 2117)
  - Yen, I (Yan Yi)
    - "The Lost," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 30, Folder 2118)
  - Yuan, K'o-chia (Yuan Kejia)
    - "Silent Bell," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 30, Folder 2119)
  - Zukofsky, Louis
    - "from 'A' - 23"
      - Typescript, 1975 May (Box 30, Folder 2120)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1975 Jul 26 (Box 30, Folder 2121)
  - Unidentified author/translator
    - [Review] "Akromacdiarmid," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2122)
    - "Autumn Song," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2123)
    - "Bugger!," typescript, 2c., undated
    - "Carol," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2124)
    - "Chidings," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2125)
    - "The Cock of Pomander Walk," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2125a)
    - "The Dragon Sings," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2126)
    - "Echo of Conscience," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2127)
    - "Elegy for W. H. Auden," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2128)
    - "A Fable," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2129)
    - "The First Dance," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2130)
    - "For Pope," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2131)
    - "from The Great Bell," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2132)
    - "Gamut," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2133)
    - "Gardening," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2134)
    - "Great Malvern," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2135)
    - "Growing," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2136)
    - "The Hag of Beare, from the 9th century Irish," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2137)
    - "Harold Monro," galley, undated (Box 31, Folder 2138)
    - [Review] "Homer, The Odyssey ," translated by Walter Shewring, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2139)
    - "Hymns. The Poet to his dead Mother," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2140)
    - "In the Garden," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2141)
    - "In transit," typescript, 2c., undated (Box 31, Folder 2142)
    - "Island of Pines," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2143)
    - "It Weeps in My Heart (After Verlaine)," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2144)
    - "J.S.B.," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2145)
    - "Kakua's Song," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2146)
    - [Review] "Kythings: Ronald Eadie Munro: Modern Scottish Poets No. 4," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2147)
    - "Looking for Laforgue," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2148)
    - "The love feast," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2149)
    - "Lullaby," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2150)
    - "Miranda," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2151)
    - "Mont Kearsarge," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2152)
    - "A New Life," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2153)
    - [Review] "Nick Malone: The Burial of Crispin Pyke...," typescript, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2154)
    - "Night Letter," typescript, 3c., undated (Box 31, Folder 2155)
    - "Oxford," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2156)
    - "I Pablo," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2157)
    - Empty folder (Box 31, Folder 2158)
    - "Rada," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2159)
    - "The Rape" autograph ms. in various hands, undated (Box 31, Folder 2160)
    - Empty folder (Box 31, Folder 2161)
    - [Review] "Reason and Energy: Studies in German Literature," edited by Michael Hamburger, typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2162)
    - "Retirement," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2163)
    - "Ritual," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2164)
    - "The Secret," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2165)
    - "LXVII," typecript, annotated, undated (Box 31, Folder 2166)
    - "Shades of the suitors, to Penelope on Ithica (shades, to the world)," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2167)
    - "Shadows," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2168)
    - "Soneto a Cristo Crucificado," printed version, undated (Box 31, Folder 2169)
      With: "464 Retrato de Lisi que tráia en una sortija," by Francisco de Quevedo and "XVIII," by Lope de Vega, printed versions, undated
    - "The Table," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2170)
    - [Review] "Tangent 6: Background Music by David Miller," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 31, Folder 2171)
    - "Thatched," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2172)
    - "This Room," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2173)
    - [Three Poems], typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2174)
    - [Three Reviews], typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2175)
    - "Three Translations," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2176)
    - "Time to Live," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2177)
    - "Trei Crai La Rasarit," typescript, with sheet music, photocopy, undated (Box 31, Folder 2178)
    - "Twin Moons," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2179)
    - [Review] "Vernon Watkins. Fidelities ," typescript, p.3 only, undated (Box 31, Folder 2180)
    - "Widowers," typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 2181)
    - Untitled article, autograph ms., undated (Box 31, Folder 2182)
    - Untitled poems, autograph ms. and typescript, 1967, undated (Box 31, Folder 2183)
- Production Files, 1969-1984; Series II; 4; (8 boxes)
  Series II, Production Files, is arranged chronologically by issue.
  - Volume 7-8, Numbers 3-1 (Wyndham Lewis Issue)
    - Notes, typescript and printed, [1969-70] (Box 32, Folder 2184)
  - Volume 9-10, Numbers 4-1 (Thomas Hardy Issue)
    - Acknowledgements, autograph ms., [1972] (Box 32, Folder 2185)
    - Fragments, typescript and printed, [1972] (Box 32, Folder 2186)
    - Galleys, corrected [incomplete], [1972] (Box 32, Folder 2187)
    - Page proofs, corrected, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 2188)
  - Volumes 10-11, Numbers 4-1 (Rhythm Issue)
    - Questionnaire, typescript, 3c., [1972-73] (Box 32, Folder 2189)
    - Responses to Questionnaire, typescript (Box 32, Folder 2190)
      - Beresford, Anne Bunting, Basil Dale, Peter Davie, Donald Dent, Peter Fuller, Roy Gunn, Thom Hamburger, Michael Heath-Stubbs, John Henri, Adrian Hill, Geoffrey Levi, Peter Macbeth, George Montague,John Patchett, John Pound, Omar Raine, Kathleen Srawley, Stephen Stallworthy, Jon Wright, David Tomlinson, Charles, [1972-73]
    - Responses to Questionnaire (Box 32, Folder 2191)
    - Empty folder (Box 32, Folder 2192)
    - Galleys, corrected, [1972-73] (Box 32, Folder 2193)
    - Page proofs [incomplete], [1972-73] (Box 32, Folder 2194)
  - Volume 11, Numbers 2-3 (American Rhythm Issue)
    - Questionnaire, typescript, [1973] (Box 32, Folder 2195)
    - Responses to Questionaire, typescript (Box 32, Folder 2196)
      - Davie, Donald Eberhart, Richard Hall, Donald Hine, Daryl Lowell, Robert Middleton, Christopher Oppen, George Snodgrass, W. D. Stafford, William, [1973]
    - Notes, typescript, [1973] (Box 32, Folder 2197)
    - Galleys, corrected, [1973] (Box 32, Folder 2198)
    - Proofs, corrected [incomplete], [1973] (Box 32, Folder 2199)
  - Volumes 11-12, Numbers 4-1 (David Jones Issue)
    - Acknowledgment, notes, and related material, typescript and printed, [1973-74] (Box 32, Folder 2200)
    - Galley, corrected, [1973-74] (Box 32, Folder 2201-2202)
    - Galley, corrected, [1973-74] (Box 32, Folder 2203)
    - Galley, corrected [incomplete], [1973-74] (Box 33, Folder 2204)
    - Proofs, corrected, [1973-74] (Box 33, Folder 2205)
  - Volume 12, Number 2
    - Acknowledgement, contents page, and notes, autograph ms., and typescript, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2206)
    - Galley, corrected, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2207)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2208)
    - Proofs, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2209)
  - Volume 12, Number 3 (Romanian Poetry Supplement)
    - Title page, contents page, noted and related material, autograph ms. and typescript, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2210)
    - Galley, corrected, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2211)
    - Galley, corrected [incomplete], 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2212)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2213)
    - Proofs, corrected [incomplete], 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2214)
  - Volumes 12-13, Numbers 4-1 (Fifteenth Anniversary Issue)
    - Notes and related material, typescript, [1975] (Box 33, Folder 2215)
    - Galley, corrected, [1975] (Box 33, Folder 2216)
    - Galley, corrected, [1975] (Box 33, Folder 2217)
    - Proofs, corrected, [1975] (Box 33, Folder 2218)
  - Volume 13, Number 2
    - Cover, contents page and related material, autograph ms., and printed, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2219)
    - Galley, corrected, [1975] (Box 34, Folder 2220)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2221)
  - Volume 13, Number 3
    - Cover, contents page, and related material, autograph ms., typescript, and printed, [1975] (Box 34, Folder 2222)
    - Galley, corrected, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2223)
    - Proofs, corrected, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2224)
  - Volumes 13-14, Numbers 4-1
    - Advertising copy and related material, typescript and printed, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2225)
    - Galley, corrected, [1976] (Box 34, Folder 2226)
    - Galley, [1976] (Box 34, Folder 2227)
    - Proof [incomplete], [1976] (Box 34, Folder 2228)
  - Volume 14, Number 2
    - Galley, corrected [incomplete], [1976] (Box 34, Folder 2229)
    - Proof with related material, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2230)
  - Volume 14, Number 3 (Criticism Issue)
    - Contents page and related material, [1976] (Box 34, Folder 2231)
    - Questionnaire, typescript, 2c., 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2232)
    - Questionnaire responses, typescript (Box 34, Folder 2233)
      - Alexander, Michael Bergonzi, Bernard Carey, John Collier, Michael Davie, Donald Empson, William Hamburger, Michael Sisson, C. H. Soames, Enoch Wainwright, Jeffrey, 1976
    - Questionnaire responses, galley, corrected, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2234)
    - Questionnaire responses, galley, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2235)
    - Galley, corrected, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2236-2237)